Hello

I'm Jacob LaMarre

6300 Sullins Rd Charlotte, NC 28214 (980)-230-1816 lordaufchaos@yahoo.com

Skills

Currently learning full-stack web development in a coding bootcamp, have novice experience with HTML/CSS and Javascript/Jquery. Also can confidently navigate the use of CSS frameworks with a good level of confidence.

I have for years been a certified pharmacy technician, experience with cold calling patients, reading medical transcription, customer service experience, empathy and active listening, relaying health information to patients, store inventory management,

Experience

December 2015 - PRESENT

CVS health, Charlotte NC- CPhT (Certified Pharmacy Technician)

- Support Staff for pharmacist, Type, Bill, Count, and Package prescriptions.
- Customer service, Ringing Sales, answering phone calls, and de escalating issues.
- Pharmacy maintenance, monitoring inventory and adjusting orders for stock drugs as needed, supply ordering, general cleaning and examining drug expiration dates.

November 2007 - December 2015

Target, Charlotte - CphT (certified Pharmacy Technician) / food service employee

- Pharmacy support staff same as present occupation
- Began working as a food service employee, prepared food, rang food sales, cleaned back of store and food preparation areas.

Education

August 2009 - May2012

Central Piedmont Community College, Charlotte- Associates Science